

# CONTACT

kkalia9@gmail.com

+91 9990360885

kanikakalia.github.io

Gurgaon, India

# **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SICENCE AND ENGINEERING

2013

Himachal Pradesh University, HP

# **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY

ANGULAR JS

REACT JS

PHOTOSHOP

#### SOCIAL

in www.linkedin.com/in/kkalia9

kanikakalia.github.io

@kkalia9

codepen.io/kkalia9

# KANIKA KALIA

UI Developer

# **ABOUT**

I am UI Developer, my skills include HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, AngularJs, React.JS, WordPress, Photoshop and various new libraries in user interface development.

In addition to these, I have 4 years of experience in Front-end development. I am always seeking new challenges that allow me to use my skills in User Experience Development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **UI DEVELOPER**

ABCplusD | Feb 2016 - Present

- Team Handling, Work distribution and management
- · Web development, Front-end designing.

#### **UI DEVELOPER**

Inventum Tecnologies Pvt Ltd | June 2015 - Feb 2016

- Web development.
- Front-end integration.
- Rest api integration with frontend.

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

IWS pvt. ltd. | June 2014 - April 2015

• Web development.

### **WEB DEVELOPER**

OSRE pvt. ltd. | July 2013 - April 2014

Web development.

#### LATEST PROJECTS

#### Dauble:

Dauble is a unique solution for all stakeholders in the Visual Arts world. Please check out www.dauble.com for more details

Technologies: Angular.Js, HTML, CSS, Webpack, Yarn, Grunt, Git

#### MuscleMatics Admin:

MuscleMatics provide's simple visual representations of the human anatomy when performing various forms of exercise, with emphasis on technique and muscles utilized. Technologies: Angular.Js, HTML, CSS, Webpack, Yarn, Grunt, Git

# Stroke Art fair (ongoing):

Website for an upcoming artfair. www.strokeartfair.com/beta

Technologies: Reactjs, JSX, React bootstrap